The Amanda Seals Show.
Hey, y'all. It's the Amanda Seals Show.
I'm Amanda Seals here, and we are joined
by one of my favorite human beings,
comedian, producer, actor, writer,
Sidney Castillo.
So, you know, I wanted to talk,
I wanted to have the friend conversation with Sidney
because Sidney's like my actual friend.
And, but I feel like we have the kind of friendship
where like we don't have to talk to each other
for like months on end,
but then when we see each other,
it'll be like lock in.
Do y'all have friends that have like,
I don't want to call them titles.
Like I'm the friend that they come,
that the crew comes to when they need encouragement.
Then there's a friend that you go to
when you want to act crazy.
You know, the friend that when you really want to get ratchet,
you know, which one she is.
We all friends though,
but everybody has a role in the thing.
So I'm not a part of a clique.
So I feel like I'm a different role to different people.
I think in general though,
like I'm the,
she going to keep it a buck with me friend.
Like I am that friend.
Like most people don't come to me
until with something,
until they're ready to receive
like the actual truth.
Then you got friends where like,
like she said,
like I got friends where I'm angry.
I know who I'm gonna call to agree with me.
I don't want the friends sometimes like Sidney.
I want the rah, rah.
Go over there, Sidney.
Go over there then.
It's at the comedy show.
The show.
Just go over there.
Like, oh, I need that friend.
And then I got my friends like Sidney, brother.
Come on, man.
Would your mom approve?
What if you go to jail?
You know, I got that guy, you know?
We up.